{"data":[{"question":"We _____ in the morning.","a":"don't come","b":"didn't come","c":"came not","d":"not came","answer":"2","explain":"- The negative form of past tense: did not + S","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"When did little Tom _____ the milk?","a":"drink","b":"drank","c":"drunk","d":"to drink","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the Infinitive verb in the question","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"When did Mr Smith _____ to London?","a":"go","b":"went","c":"gone","d":"to go","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the infinitive verb in the question","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"She _____ to the cinema.","a":"not went","b":"didn't went","c":"didn't go","d":"doesn't went","answer":"3","explain":"- The negative form: did not + V-infinitive","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"What did Carol _____ last sunday?","a":"do","b":"did","c":"done","d":"X","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the infinitive in the question","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"Which of the following is correct?","a":"Played you cricket?","b":"Did play you cricket?","c":"Did you play cricket?","d":"Did you played cricket?","answer":"3","explain":"- The yes\/no question","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"_____ champagne on Christmas eve?","a":"Did you drink","b":"Drank you","c":"Did drink you","d":"Did you drank","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the question form: Did + S + V..?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"We _____ the football match.","a":"didn't win","b":"didn't won","c":"don't win","d":"don't won","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the negative form: did not + V-infinitive","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"Which of the following is correct?","a":"Worked she very hard?","b":"Did work she very hard?","c":"Did she work very hard?","d":"Did she worked very hard?","answer":"3","explain":"- The yes\/ no question","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"What _____ last Sunday?","a":"you did","b":"did you did","c":"did you","d":"did you do","answer":"4","explain":"Using the question form","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"}]}